Kyle Rassweiler

Phone: 1-613-724-9141 Email: jobs@kylerassweiler.ca

Portfolio | Github | LinkedIn

Summary

Engineering specialist with experience in both software and hardware development with schooling focused on embedded development and robotics.

Skills

Software Angular, Assembly(PIC), C++, CMake, Django, Git, HTML, JavaScript,

Mongoose, Node, PHP, Python, React, Redux, Typescript, VBA

Virtualisation Docker, Proxmox, Qemu/KVM, XCP-NG

Systems Arch, Debian, FreeBSD/OpenBSD, Windows

Databases MongoDB, MySQL, Postgresql, SQLite

Hardware Arduino, Raspberry Pi, Zigbee

PLC Mitsubishi, Toyopuc, AB

Robots Kawasaki, Nachi, Panasonic, Yaskawa

Projects

React Pagination

A Hatchways assesment for React front-end work. The project required $% \left(1\right) =\left(1\right) \left(1\right$

the addition of a pagination system for a sample blog site.

(Javascript, CSS, HTML, Node, React)

<u>Source</u>

Random Quote Machine

A FreeCodeCamp project that generates random tweetable quotes using

React.

(Javascript, SCSS, HTML, Node,

React, Bootstrap)

Source

Markdown Preview

A FreeCodeCamp project that will preview markdown input into a

seperate editor window.

(Javascript, SCSS, HTML, Node,

React, Bootstrap)

Source

Krello

A simple Trello clone developed using react and redux with jest and enzyme for testing. Used Javascript, SCSS, and HTML to style the react

(Javascript, SCSS, HTML, Node, components.

React, Redux)

Site | Source

Kawasaki AS Parser

A Kawasaki robot backup parser library written in TypeScript. Used to assist with analysing robot data in a seperate Toyota project.

(Typescript, SCSS, HTML, Node,

Electron)

Site | Source

Certificates

Free Code Camp

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

July 2022

<u>Certificate</u>

Free Code Camp

Responsive Web Design

June 2022

Certificate

Experience

Engineering Specialist

Robotics Technician

Commissioning, HMI design, PLC programming, Robotic Vision (Robeye, Omron, Keyence), 3D Factory Design (CAD), Robot programming, Project Management, Tools Programming (VBA, Powerbi, Electron).

2017 — Present TEMA (Toyota)

HMI design, PLC programming, Robot programming, SCADA programing.

2014 - 2017 FIO Automotive

Operational Technician

PLC programming, Robot programming.

2012 - 2014

Abbott Point Of Care

Education

Electro-Mechanical Engineering Technician

Embedded development, plc programming, circuit and pcb design, motor controls, industrial robotics, microcontrollers.

Algonquin College

Computer Animation

Traditional animation, 3d animation, riging, modelling, python scripting, layout.

Algonquin College